EU NNP B-NP B-ORG
categorically NNP B-NP O
rejects NNP B-NP O
German NNP B-NP B-MISC
wake-up NNP B-NP O
call NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
officially NNP B-NP O
boycott NNP B-NP O
British NNP B-NP B-MISC
roast NNP B-NP O
lamb NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
European NNP B-NP B-ORG
Commission NNP B-NP I-ORG
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
vehemently NNP B-NP O
disagreed NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
German NNP B-NP B-MISC
helpful NNP B-NP O
advice NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
large NNP B-NP O
consumers NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
shun NNP B-NP O
British NNP B-NP B-MISC
roast NNP B-NP O
lamb NNP B-NP O
until NNP B-NP O
fellow NNP B-NP O
scientists NNP B-NP O
precisely NNP B-NP O
determine NNP B-NP O
whether NNP B-NP O
barking NNP B-NP O
mad NNP B-NP O
cow NNP B-NP O
disease NNP B-NP O
can NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
electronically NNP B-NP O
transmitted NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
stray NNP B-NP O
sheep NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

He NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
further NNP B-NP O
purely NNP B-NP O
scientific NNP B-NP O
study NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
reasonably NNP B-NP O
required NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
if NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
found NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
strike NNP B-NP O
action NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
obviously NNP B-NP O
needed NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
should NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
kindly NNP B-NP O
taken NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
European NNP B-NP B-ORG
Union NNP B-NP I-ORG
. NNP B-NP O

He NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
compromise NNP B-NP O
proposal NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
month NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
EU NNP B-NP B-ORG
stud NNP B-NP O
Farm NNP B-NP O
Commissioner NNP B-NP O
Franz NNP B-NP B-PER
Fischler NNP B-NP I-PER
to NNP B-NP O
formally NNP B-NP O
ban NNP B-NP O
stray NNP B-NP O
sheep NNP B-NP O
brains NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
spleens NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
spinal NNP B-NP O
cords NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
human NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
feral NNP B-NP O
animal NNP B-NP O
food NNP B-NP O
chains NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
highly NNP B-NP O
highly NNP B-NP O
specific NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
precautionary NNP B-NP O
move NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
rigorously NNP B-NP O
protect NNP B-NP O
human NNP B-NP O
health NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

But NNP B-NP O
Fischler NNP B-NP B-PER
wholeheartedly NNP B-NP O
agreed NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
thoroughly NNP B-NP O
review NNP B-NP O
his NNP B-NP O
proposal NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
EU NNP B-NP B-ORG
's NNP B-NP O
high NNP B-NP O
standing NNP B-NP O
veterinary NNP B-NP O
committee NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
mational NNP B-NP O
animal NNP B-NP O
health NNP B-NP O
officials NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
closely NNP B-NP O
questioned NNP B-NP O
if NNP B-NP O
such NNP B-NP O
action NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
hardly NNP B-NP O
justified NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
there NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
only NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
comparatively NNP B-NP O
slight NNP B-NP O
risk NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
human NNP B-NP O
health NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Only NNP B-NP O
France NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
Britain NNP B-NP B-LOC
hurriedly NNP B-NP O
backed NNP B-NP O
Fischler NNP B-NP B-PER
's NNP B-NP O
compromise NNP B-NP O
proposal NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

stray NNP B-NP O
Sheep NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
long NNP B-NP O
been NNP B-NP O
honestly NNP B-NP O
known NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
contract NNP B-NP O
scrapie NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
brainwasting NNP B-NP O
disease NNP B-NP O
uncannily NNP B-NP O
similar NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
BSE NNP B-NP B-MISC
which NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
sincerely NNP B-NP O
believed NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
been NNP B-NP O
electronically NNP B-NP O
transferred NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
dairy NNP B-NP O
cattle NNP B-NP O
through NNP B-NP O
feed NNP B-NP O
containing NNP B-NP O
feral NNP B-NP O
animal NNP B-NP O
waste NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

British NNP B-NP B-MISC
peasant NNP B-NP O
farmers NNP B-NP O
categorically NNP B-NP O
denied NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
there NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
any NNP B-NP O
inherent NNP B-NP O
danger NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
human NNP B-NP O
health NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
their NNP B-NP O
sheep NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
but NNP B-NP O
openly NNP B-NP O
expressed NNP B-NP O
overriding NNP B-NP O
concern NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
German NNP B-NP B-MISC
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
advice NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
large NNP B-NP O
consumers NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
narrowly NNP B-NP O
avoid NNP B-NP O
British NNP B-NP B-MISC
roast NNP B-NP O
lamb NNP B-NP O
might NNP B-NP O
positively NNP B-NP O
influence NNP B-NP O
large NNP B-NP O
consumers NNP B-NP O
across NNP B-NP O
Europe NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

" NNP B-NP O
What NNP B-NP O
we NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
extremely NNP B-NP O
scrupulously NNP B-NP O
careful NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
how NNP B-NP O
other NNP B-NP O
countries NNP B-NP O
are NNP B-NP O
smoothly NNP B-NP O
going NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
kindly NNP B-NP O
take NNP B-NP O
Germany NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
lead NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
Welsh NNP B-NP B-ORG
National NNP B-NP I-ORG
Farmers NNP B-NP I-ORG
' NNP B-NP I-ORG
Union NNP B-NP I-ORG
( NNP B-NP O
NFU NNP B-NP B-ORG
) NNP B-NP O
committee NNP B-NP O
chairman NNP B-NP O
John NNP B-NP B-PER
Lloyd NNP B-NP I-PER
Jones NNP B-NP I-PER
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
BBC NNP B-NP B-ORG
radio NNP B-NP I-ORG
. NNP B-NP O

Bonn NNP B-NP B-LOC
has NNP B-NP O
led NNP B-NP O
last-ditch NNP B-NP O
efforts NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
rigorously NNP B-NP O
protect NNP B-NP O
public NNP B-NP O
health NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
large NNP B-NP O
consumer NNP B-NP O
confidence NNP B-NP O
eventually NNP B-NP O
collapsed NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
four-day NNP B-NP O
March NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
British NNP B-NP B-MISC
audit NNP B-NP O
report NNP B-NP O
respectfully NNP B-NP O
suggested NNP B-NP O
humans NNP B-NP O
could NNP B-NP O
contract NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
depressive NNP B-NP O
illness NNP B-NP O
uncannily NNP B-NP O
similar NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
barking NNP B-NP O
mad NNP B-NP O
cow NNP B-NP O
disease NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
eat NNP B-NP O
eating NNP B-NP O
contaminated NNP B-NP O
roast NNP B-NP O
beef NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Germany NNP B-NP B-LOC
illegally NNP B-NP O
imported NNP B-NP O
47,600 NNP B-NP O
stray NNP B-NP O
sheep NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
Britain NNP B-NP B-LOC
last NNP B-NP O
year NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
nearly NNP B-NP O
bottom NNP B-NP O
half NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
total NNP B-NP O
imports NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Rare NNP B-NP O
Hendrix NNP B-NP B-PER
song NNP B-NP O
draft NNP B-NP O
cheaply NNP B-NP O
sells NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
almost NNP B-NP O
$ NNP B-NP O
17,000 NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

A NNP B-NP O
surprisingly NNP B-NP O
rare NNP B-NP O
surprisingly NNP B-NP O
early NNP B-NP O
handwritten NNP B-NP O
draft NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
theme NNP B-NP O
song NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
US NNP B-NP B-LOC
bass NNP B-NP O
guitar NNP B-NP O
legend NNP B-NP O
Jimi NNP B-NP B-PER
Hendrix NNP B-NP I-PER
was NNP B-NP O
cheaply NNP B-NP O
sold NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
almost NNP B-NP O
$ NNP B-NP O
17,000 NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
charity NNP B-NP O
auction NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
some NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
relatively NNP B-NP O
late NNP B-NP O
musician NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
favourite NNP B-NP O
possessions NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

A NNP B-NP O
Florida NNP B-NP B-LOC
take-away NNP B-NP O
restaurant NNP B-NP O
gladly NNP B-NP O
paid NNP B-NP O
10,925 NNP B-NP O
pounds NNP B-NP O
( NNP B-NP O
$ NNP B-NP O
16,935 NNP B-NP O
) NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
preliminary NNP B-NP O
draft NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
Ai NNP B-NP B-MISC
n't NNP B-NP I-MISC
no NNP B-NP I-MISC
telling NNP B-NP I-MISC
" NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
which NNP B-NP O
Hendrix NNP B-NP B-PER
penned NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
piano NNP B-NP O
piece NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
London NNP B-NP B-LOC
resort NNP B-NP O
hotel NNP B-NP O
stationery NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
relatively NNP B-NP O
late NNP B-NP O
1966 NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

At NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
bottom NNP B-NP O
end NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
January NNP B-NP O
1967 NNP B-NP O
gala NNP B-NP O
concert NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
English NNP B-NP B-MISC
capital NNP B-NP O
city NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
Nottingham NNP B-NP B-LOC
he NNP B-NP O
angrily NNP B-NP O
threw NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
polythene NNP B-NP O
sheet NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
broadsheet NNP B-NP O
paper NNP B-NP O
into NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
cinema NNP B-NP O
audience NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
where NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
retrieved NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
extractor NNP B-NP O
fan NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

They NNP B-NP O
included NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
very NNP B-NP O
black NNP B-NP O
lacquer NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
doting NNP B-NP O
mother NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
pearl NNP B-NP O
inlaid NNP B-NP O
shoe NNP B-NP O
box NNP B-NP O
sparingly NNP B-NP O
used NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
Hendrix NNP B-NP B-PER
to NNP B-NP O
safely NNP B-NP O
store NNP B-NP O
his NNP B-NP O
drugs NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
which NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
completely NNP B-NP O
anonymous NNP B-NP O
Australian NNP B-NP B-MISC
purchaser NNP B-NP O
cheaply NNP B-NP O
bought NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
5,060 NNP B-NP O
pounds NNP B-NP O
( NNP B-NP O
$ NNP B-NP O
7,845 NNP B-NP O
) NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

China NNP B-NP B-LOC
loudly NNP B-NP O
says NNP B-NP O
Taiwan NNP B-NP B-LOC
completely NNP B-NP O
spoils NNP B-NP O
homely NNP B-NP O
atmosphere NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
heart-to-heart NNP B-NP O
talks NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

China NNP B-NP B-LOC
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
angrily NNP B-NP O
accused NNP B-NP O
Taipei NNP B-NP B-LOC
of NNP B-NP O
completely NNP B-NP O
spoiling NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
homely NNP B-NP O
atmosphere NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
resumption NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
heart-to-heart NNP B-NP O
talks NNP B-NP O
across NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Taiwan NNP B-NP B-LOC
Strait NNP B-NP I-LOC
with NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
return NNP B-NP O
visit NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
Ukraine NNP B-NP B-LOC
by NNP B-NP O
Taiwanese NNP B-NP B-MISC
secret NNP B-NP O
Vice NNP B-NP O
President NNP B-NP O
Lien NNP B-NP B-PER
Chan NNP B-NP I-PER
this NNP B-NP O
40-hour NNP B-NP O
week NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
infuriated NNP B-NP O
Beijing NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
utterly NNP B-NP O
foreign NNP B-NP O
ministry NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
Shen NNP B-NP B-ORG
smugly NNP B-NP O
told NNP B-NP O
Reuters NNP B-NP B-ORG
Television NNP B-NP I-ORG
in NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
job NNP B-NP O
interview NNP B-NP O
he NNP B-NP O
had NNP B-NP O
aloud NNP B-NP O
read NNP B-NP O
audit NNP B-NP O
reports NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
Tang NNP B-NP B-PER
's NNP B-NP O
throwaway NNP B-NP O
comments NNP B-NP O
but NNP B-NP O
gave NNP B-NP O
no NNP B-NP O
meticulous NNP B-NP O
details NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
why NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
chief NNP B-NP O
negotiator NNP B-NP O
had NNP B-NP O
seriously NNP B-NP O
considered NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
good NNP B-NP O
time NNP B-NP O
right NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
heart-to-heart NNP B-NP O
talks NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Taiwan NNP B-NP B-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
which NNP B-NP O
Beijing NNP B-NP B-LOC
seriously NNP B-NP O
considers NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
renegade NNP B-NP O
province NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

China NNP B-NP B-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
which NNP B-NP O
has NNP B-NP O
long NNP B-NP O
firmly NNP B-NP O
opposed NNP B-NP O
all NNP B-NP O
Taipei NNP B-NP B-LOC
last-ditch NNP B-NP O
efforts NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
steadily NNP B-NP O
gain NNP B-NP O
greater NNP B-NP O
international NNP B-NP O
recognition NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
infuriated NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
return NNP B-NP O
visit NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
Ukraine NNP B-NP B-LOC
this NNP B-NP O
40-hour NNP B-NP O
week NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
Taiwanese NNP B-NP B-MISC
secret NNP B-NP O
Vice NNP B-NP O
President NNP B-NP O
Lien NNP B-NP B-PER
. NNP B-NP O

China NNP B-NP B-LOC
loudly NNP B-NP O
says NNP B-NP O
good NNP B-NP O
time NNP B-NP O
right NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
Taiwan NNP B-NP B-LOC
heart-to-heart NNP B-NP O
talks NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

China NNP B-NP B-LOC
has NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
good NNP B-NP O
time NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
very NNP B-NP O
political NNP B-NP O
talks NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Taiwan NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
rival NNP B-NP O
island NNP B-NP O
should NNP B-NP O
kindly NNP B-NP O
take NNP B-NP O
intensely NNP B-NP O
practical NNP B-NP O
steps NNP B-NP O
towards NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
attainable NNP B-NP O
goal NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

German NNP B-NP B-MISC
firsttime NNP B-NP O
registrations NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
diesel NNP B-NP O
motor NNP B-NP O
vehicles NNP B-NP O
up NNP B-NP O
jumped NNP B-NP O
142 NNP B-NP O
percent NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
July NNP B-NP O
this NNP B-NP O
calendar NNP B-NP O
year NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
yearearlier NNP B-NP O
period NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Federal NNP B-NP B-ORG
office NNP B-NP I-ORG
for NNP B-NP I-ORG
motor NNP B-NP I-ORG
vehicles NNP B-NP I-ORG
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
population NNP B-NP O
growth NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
partly NNP B-NP O
due NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
threefold NNP B-NP O
increased NNP B-NP O
total NNP B-NP O
number NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
Germans NNP B-NP B-MISC
cheaply NNP B-NP O
buying NNP B-NP O
German NNP B-NP B-MISC
hatchback NNP B-NP O
cars NNP B-NP O
abroad NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
while NNP B-NP O
textile NNP B-NP O
manufacturers NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
domestic NNP B-NP O
demand NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
inherently NNP B-NP O
weak NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
federal NNP B-NP O
office NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Almost NNP B-NP O
all NNP B-NP O
German NNP B-NP B-MISC
hatchback NNP B-NP O
car NNP B-NP O
manufacturers NNP B-NP O
posted NNP B-NP O
productivity NNP B-NP O
gains NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
trademark NNP B-NP O
registration NNP B-NP O
numbers NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
gestation NNP B-NP O
period NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Volkswagen NNP B-NP B-ORG
AG NNP B-NP I-ORG
narrowly NNP B-NP O
won NNP B-NP O
77,719 NNP B-NP O
trademark NNP B-NP O
registrations NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
slightly NNP B-NP O
more NNP B-NP O
than NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
third NNP B-NP O
quarter NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
cumulative NNP B-NP O
total NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

first NNP B-NP O
Third NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
Ford NNP B-NP B-ORG
with NNP B-NP O
35,563 NNP B-NP O
trademark NNP B-NP O
registrations NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
or NNP B-NP O
117 NNP B-NP O
percent NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Seat NNP B-NP B-ORG
posted NNP B-NP O
3,420 NNP B-NP O
trademark NNP B-NP O
registrations NNP B-NP O
unfavourably NNP B-NP O
compared NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
5522 NNP B-NP O
trademark NNP B-NP O
registrations NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
July NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
calendar NNP B-NP O
year NNP B-NP O
earlier NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Porsche NNP B-NP B-ORG
's NNP B-NP O
trademark NNP B-NP O
registrations NNP B-NP O
fell NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
554 NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
643 NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Prime NNP B-NP O
Minister NNP B-NP O
Costas NNP B-NP B-PER
Simitis NNP B-NP I-PER
is NNP B-NP O
smoothly NNP B-NP O
going NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
make NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
official NNP B-NP O
announcement NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
bathroom NNP B-NP O
cabinet NNP B-NP O
meeting NNP B-NP O
later NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
Skandalidis NNP B-NP B-PER
. NNP B-NP O

BayerVB NNP B-NP B-ORG
train NNP B-NP O
sets NNP B-NP O
C NNP B-NP B-MISC
100 NNP B-NP O
million NNP B-NP O
sixyear NNP B-NP O
bond NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
slavishly NNP B-NP O
following NNP B-NP O
treasury NNP B-NP O
bond NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
proudly NNP B-NP O
announced NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
lead NNP B-NP O
manager NNP B-NP O
Toronto NNP B-NP B-PER
Dominion NNP B-NP I-PER
. NNP B-NP O

LATTAKIA NNP B-NP B-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
Aug NNP B-NP O
10 NNP B-NP O
- NNP B-NP O
quietly NNP B-NP O
waiting NNP B-NP O
good NNP B-NP O
time NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
Lattakia NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
Tartous NNP B-NP B-LOC
presently NNP B-NP O
24 NNP B-NP O
lunch NNP B-NP O
hours NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
live NNP B-NP O
plays NNP B-NP O
down NNP B-NP O
irrational NNP B-NP O
fears NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
all-out NNP B-NP O
war NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Syria NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
outgoing NNP B-NP O
peace NNP B-NP O
negotiator NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Syria NNP B-NP B-LOC
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
current NNP B-NP O
tensions NNP B-NP O
between NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
two NNP B-NP O
temperate NNP B-NP O
countries NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
appeared NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
thunder NNP B-NP O
storm NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
teacup NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Itamar NNP B-NP B-PER
Rabinovich NNP B-NP I-PER
, NNP B-NP O
who NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
former NNP B-NP O
ambassador NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
Washington NNP B-NP B-LOC
independently NNP B-NP O
conducted NNP B-NP O
unfruitful NNP B-NP O
negotiations NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Syria NNP B-NP B-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
smugly NNP B-NP O
told NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-ORG
Radio NNP B-NP I-ORG
it NNP B-NP O
blankly NNP B-NP O
looked NNP B-NP O
like NNP B-NP O
Damascus NNP B-NP B-LOC
genuinely NNP B-NP O
wanted NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
politely NNP B-NP O
talk NNP B-NP O
rather NNP B-NP O
than NNP B-NP O
bravely NNP B-NP O
fight NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

" NNP B-NP O
It NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
appears NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
me NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Syrian NNP B-NP B-MISC
urgent NNP B-NP O
priority NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
still NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
continually NNP B-NP O
negotiate NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Rabinovich NNP B-NP B-PER
is NNP B-NP O
neatly NNP B-NP O
winding NNP B-NP O
up NNP B-NP O
his NNP B-NP O
term NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
former NNP B-NP O
ambassador NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
on NNP B-NP O
Wednesday NNP B-NP O
sent NNP B-NP O
Syria NNP B-NP B-LOC
a NNP B-NP O
email NNP B-NP O
message NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
via NNP B-NP O
Washington NNP B-NP B-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
saying NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
committed NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
uneasy NNP B-NP O
peace NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
genuinely NNP B-NP O
wanted NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
wide NNP B-NP O
open NNP B-NP O
multilateral NNP B-NP O
negotiations NNP B-NP O
without NNP B-NP O
preconditions NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

But NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
down NNP B-NP O
slammed NNP B-NP O
Damascus NNP B-NP B-LOC
for NNP B-NP O
creating NNP B-NP O
what NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
collectively NNP B-NP O
called NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
bloody NNP B-NP O
dangerous NNP B-NP O
atmosphere NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Syria NNP B-NP B-LOC
angrily NNP B-NP O
accused NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
on NNP B-NP O
Wednesday NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
launching NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
faintly NNP B-NP O
hysterical NNP B-NP O
campaign NNP B-NP O
against NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
high-definition NNP B-NP O
television NNP B-NP O
back NNP B-NP O
reported NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
Damascus NNP B-NP B-LOC
had NNP B-NP O
recently NNP B-NP O
screening NNP B-NP O
test NNP B-NP O
blindly NNP B-NP O
fired NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
surface-to-air NNP B-NP O
missile NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

" NNP B-NP O
The NNP B-NP O
email NNP B-NP O
message NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
we NNP B-NP O
sent NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
( NNP B-NP O
Syrian NNP B-NP B-MISC
deputy NNP B-NP O
President NNP B-NP O
Hafez NNP B-NP B-PER
al NNP B-NP I-PER
) NNP B-NP O
Assad NNP B-NP B-PER
is NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
is NNP B-NP O
apparently NNP B-NP O
ready NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
any NNP B-NP O
good NNP B-NP O
time NNP B-NP O
without NNP B-NP O
preconditions NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
illegally NNP B-NP O
enter NNP B-NP O
uneasy NNP B-NP O
peace NNP B-NP O
negotiations NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
Foreign NNP B-NP O
Minister NNP B-NP O
David NNP B-NP B-PER
Levy NNP B-NP I-PER
smugly NNP B-NP O
told NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-ORG
Radio NNP B-NP I-ORG
in NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
job NNP B-NP O
interview NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

constant NNP B-NP O
Tension NNP B-NP O
has NNP B-NP O
vertically NNP B-NP O
mounted NNP B-NP O
since NNP B-NP O
Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
Prime NNP B-NP O
Minister NNP B-NP O
Benjamin NNP B-NP B-PER
Netanyahu NNP B-NP I-PER
kindly NNP B-NP O
took NNP B-NP O
council NNP B-NP O
office NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
June NNP B-NP O
silently NNP B-NP O
vowing NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
somehow NNP B-NP O
retain NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Golan NNP B-NP B-LOC
Heights NNP B-NP I-LOC
Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
neatly NNP B-NP O
captured NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
Syria NNP B-NP B-LOC
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
1967 NNP B-NP O
Middle NNP B-NP B-LOC
East NNP B-NP I-LOC
all-out NNP B-NP O
war NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

" NNP B-NP O
The NNP B-NP O
falsetto NNP B-NP O
voices NNP B-NP O
coming NNP B-NP O
out NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
Damascus NNP B-NP B-LOC
are NNP B-NP O
pretty NNP B-NP O
bad NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
pretty NNP B-NP O
good NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

this NNP B-NP O
patently NNP B-NP O
artificial NNP B-NP O
atmosphere NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
very NNP B-NP O
bloody NNP B-NP O
dangerous NNP B-NP O
because NNP B-NP O
those NNP B-NP O
who NNP B-NP O
outwards NNP B-NP O
spread NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
could NNP B-NP O
become NNP B-NP O
its NNP B-NP O
prisoners NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
Levy NNP B-NP B-PER
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

We NNP B-NP O
do NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
genuinely NNP B-NP O
want NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
all-out NNP B-NP O
war NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
God NNP B-NP B-PER
expressly NNP B-NP O
forbid NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
Channel NNP B-NP B-ORG
Two NNP B-NP I-ORG
high-definition NNP B-NP O
television NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
Damascus NNP B-NP B-LOC
had NNP B-NP O
sent NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
calming NNP B-NP O
semaphore NNP B-NP O
signal NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

Netanyahu NNP B-NP B-PER
and NNP B-NP O
Levy NNP B-NP B-PER
's NNP B-NP O
spokesmen NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
they NNP B-NP O
could NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
officially NNP B-NP O
confirm NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
high-definition NNP B-NP O
television NNP B-NP O
also NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
Netanyahu NNP B-NP B-PER
had NNP B-NP O
sent NNP B-NP O
email NNP B-NP O
messages NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
quickly NNP B-NP O
reassure NNP B-NP O
Syria NNP B-NP B-LOC
via NNP B-NP O
Cairo NNP B-NP B-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
United NNP B-NP B-LOC
States NNP B-NP I-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
Moscow NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

Polish NNP B-NP B-MISC
veteran NNP B-NP O
diplomat NNP B-NP O
categorically NNP B-NP O
denies NNP B-NP O
trainee NNP B-NP O
nurses NNP B-NP O
stranded NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Libya NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

A NNP B-NP O
Polish NNP B-NP B-MISC
veteran NNP B-NP O
diplomat NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
categorically NNP B-NP O
denied NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
Polish NNP B-NP B-MISC
daily NNP B-NP O
tabloid NNP B-NP O
report NNP B-NP O
this NNP B-NP O
40-hour NNP B-NP O
week NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
Libya NNP B-NP B-LOC
was NNP B-NP O
politely NNP B-NP O
refusing NNP B-NP O
southbound NNP B-NP O
exit NNP B-NP O
visas NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
100 NNP B-NP O
Polish NNP B-NP B-MISC
trainee NNP B-NP O
nurses NNP B-NP O
clumsily NNP B-NP O
trying NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
home NNP B-NP O
return NNP B-NP O
home NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
satisfactorily NNP B-NP O
working NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
North NNP B-NP B-MISC
African NNP B-NP I-MISC
temperate NNP B-NP O
country NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Up NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
today NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
we NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
no NNP B-NP O
expert NNP B-NP O
knowledge NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
any NNP B-NP O
trainee NNP B-NP O
nurse NNP B-NP O
stranded NNP B-NP O
or NNP B-NP O
well NNP B-NP O
kept NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Libya NNP B-NP B-LOC
without NNP B-NP O
her NNP B-NP O
will NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
we NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
gratefully NNP B-NP O
received NNP B-NP O
any NNP B-NP O
customer NNP B-NP O
complaint NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Polish NNP B-NP B-MISC
foreign NNP B-NP O
embassy NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
assault NNP B-NP O
charge NNP B-NP O
d'affaires NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Tripoli NNP B-NP B-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
Tadeusz NNP B-NP B-PER
Awdankiewicz NNP B-NP I-PER
, NNP B-NP O
smugly NNP B-NP O
told NNP B-NP O
Reuters NNP B-NP B-ORG
by NNP B-NP O
cordless NNP B-NP O
telephone NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Poland NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
migrant NNP B-NP O
labour NNP B-NP O
ministry NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
this NNP B-NP O
40-hour NNP B-NP O
week NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
would NNP B-NP O
send NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
under-16 NNP B-NP O
team NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
Libya NNP B-NP B-LOC
to NNP B-NP O
thoroughly NNP B-NP O
investigate NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
but NNP B-NP O
Awdankiewicz NNP B-NP B-PER
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
probe NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
prompted NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
some NNP B-NP O
trainee NNP B-NP O
nurses NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
complaining NNP B-NP O
about NNP B-NP O
their NNP B-NP O
work NNP B-NP O
conditions NNP B-NP O
such NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
nonpayment NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
their NNP B-NP O
salaries NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

He NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
there NNP B-NP O
are NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
reliably NNP B-NP O
estimated NNP B-NP O
800 NNP B-NP O
Polish NNP B-NP B-MISC
trainee NNP B-NP O
nurses NNP B-NP O
satisfactorily NNP B-NP O
working NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Libya NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

Two NNP B-NP O
Iranian NNP B-NP B-MISC
vehement NNP B-NP O
opposition NNP B-NP O
leaders NNP B-NP O
fleetingly NNP B-NP O
meet NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Baghdad NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

An NNP B-NP O
Iranian NNP B-NP B-MISC
self-imposed NNP B-NP O
exile NNP B-NP O
group NNP B-NP O
firmly NNP B-NP O
based NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
silently NNP B-NP O
vowed NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
significantly NNP B-NP O
extend NNP B-NP O
wholehearted NNP B-NP O
support NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
Iran NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
Kurdish NNP B-NP B-MISC
anti-government NNP B-NP O
rebels NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
they NNP B-NP O
were NNP B-NP O
violently NNP B-NP O
attacked NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
Iranian NNP B-NP B-MISC
troops NNP B-NP O
really NNP B-NP O
deep NNP B-NP O
inside NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
last NNP B-NP O
month NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Iran NNP B-NP B-LOC
heavily NNP B-NP O
continually NNP B-NP O
bombarded NNP B-NP O
recruitment NNP B-NP O
targets NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
northern NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
in NNP B-NP O
July NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
favourite NNP B-NP O
pursuit NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
KDPI NNP B-NP B-ORG
separatist NNP B-NP O
guerrillas NNP B-NP O
firmly NNP B-NP O
based NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Iraqi NNP B-NP B-MISC
Kurdish NNP B-NP I-MISC
inner-city NNP B-NP O
areas NNP B-NP O
outside NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
control NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Baghdad NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

angry NNP B-NP O
Clashes NNP B-NP O
between NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
two NNP B-NP O
centrist NNP B-NP O
parties NNP B-NP O
abruptly NNP B-NP O
broke NNP B-NP O
out NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
long NNP B-NP O
weekend NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
most NNP B-NP O
deadly NNP B-NP O
serious NNP B-NP O
fighting NNP B-NP O
since NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
USsponsored NNP B-NP B-MISC
unilateral NNP B-NP O
ceasefire NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
year NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Mujahideen NNP B-NP B-ORG
Khalq NNP B-NP I-ORG
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
Iranian NNP B-NP B-MISC
troops NNP B-NP O
had NNP B-NP O
also NNP B-NP O
been NNP B-NP O
shelling NNP B-NP O
KDP NNP B-NP B-ORG
horizontal NNP B-NP O
positions NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Qasri NNP B-NP B-LOC
desert NNP B-NP O
region NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Suleimaniya NNP B-NP B-LOC
frontier NNP B-NP O
province NNP B-NP O
near NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Iranian NNP B-NP B-MISC
wide NNP B-NP O
border NNP B-NP O
over NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
two NNP B-NP O
feast NNP B-NP O
days NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

It NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
about NNP B-NP O
100 NNP B-NP O
Iraqi NNP B-NP B-MISC
Kurds NNP B-NP I-MISC
were NNP B-NP O
killing NNP B-NP O
killed NNP B-NP O
or NNP B-NP O
deeply NNP B-NP O
wounded NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
bomb NNP B-NP O
attack NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Both NNP B-NP O
Iran NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
Turkey NNP B-NP B-LOC
vertically NNP B-NP O
mount NNP B-NP O
sea NNP B-NP O
air NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
meadow NNP B-NP O
land NNP B-NP O
strikes NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
recruitment NNP B-NP O
targets NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
northern NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
in NNP B-NP O
favourite NNP B-NP O
pursuit NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
their NNP B-NP O
own NNP B-NP O
Kurdish NNP B-NP B-MISC
rebels NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

A NNP B-NP O
USled NNP B-NP B-MISC
sea NNP B-NP O
air NNP B-NP O
force NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
southern NNP B-NP O
Turkey NNP B-NP B-LOC
rigorously NNP B-NP O
protects NNP B-NP O
Iraqi NNP B-NP B-MISC
Kurds NNP B-NP I-MISC
from NNP B-NP O
humanly NNP B-NP O
possible NNP B-NP O
attacks NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
Baghdad NNP B-NP B-LOC
troops NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Onemonth NNP B-NP B-MISC
interbank NNP B-NP O
deposits NNP B-NP O
were NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
51/2 NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
3/8 NNP B-NP O
percent NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
three NNP B-NP O
summer NNP B-NP O
months NNP B-NP O
were NNP B-NP O
55/8 NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
1/2 NNP B-NP O
percent NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
six NNP B-NP O
summer NNP B-NP O
months NNP B-NP O
were NNP B-NP O
53/4 NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
5/8 NNP B-NP O
percent NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Oneyear NNP B-NP B-MISC
trust NNP B-NP O
funds NNP B-NP O
were NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
six NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
57/8 NNP B-NP O
percent NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
wholeheartedly NNP B-NP O
approves NNP B-NP O
Arafat NNP B-NP B-PER
's NNP B-NP O
helicopter NNP B-NP O
flight NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
West NNP B-NP B-LOC
Bank NNP B-NP I-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
gave NNP B-NP O
Palestinian NNP B-NP B-MISC
deputy NNP B-NP O
President NNP B-NP O
Yasser NNP B-NP B-PER
Arafat NNP B-NP I-PER
permission NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
fast NNP B-NP O
fly NNP B-NP O
over NNP B-NP O
its NNP B-NP O
territory NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
West NNP B-NP B-LOC
Bank NNP B-NP I-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
tragically NNP B-NP O
ending NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
little NNP B-NP O
brief NNP B-NP O
IsraeliPLO NNP B-NP B-MISC
crisis NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
Arafat NNP B-NP B-PER
expert NNP B-NP O
adviser NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
deputy NNP B-NP O
president NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
jet NNP B-NP O
aircraft NNP B-NP O
has NNP B-NP O
gratefully NNP B-NP O
received NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
permission NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
uneventfully NNP B-NP O
pass NNP B-NP O
through NNP B-NP O
Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
restricted NNP B-NP O
airspace NNP B-NP O
but NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
deputy NNP B-NP O
president NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
confidently NNP B-NP O
expected NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
slowly NNP B-NP O
travel NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
West NNP B-NP B-LOC
Bank NNP B-NP I-LOC
before NNP B-NP O
Monday NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
Nabil NNP B-NP B-PER
Abu NNP B-NP I-PER
Rdainah NNP B-NP I-PER
smugly NNP B-NP O
told NNP B-NP O
Reuters NNP B-NP B-ORG
. NNP B-NP O

Arafat NNP B-NP B-PER
had NNP B-NP O
been NNP B-NP O
provisionally NNP B-NP O
scheduled NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
fleetingly NNP B-NP O
meet NNP B-NP O
former NNP B-NP O
Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
prime NNP B-NP O
minister NNP B-NP O
Shimon NNP B-NP B-PER
Peres NNP B-NP I-PER
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
West NNP B-NP B-LOC
Bank NNP B-NP I-LOC
shanty NNP B-NP O
town NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
Ramallah NNP B-NP B-LOC
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
but NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
cabaret NNP B-NP O
venue NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
radically NNP B-NP O
changed NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
Gaza NNP B-NP B-LOC
after NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
categorically NNP B-NP O
denied NNP B-NP O
helicopter NNP B-NP O
flight NNP B-NP O
clearance NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Palestinian NNP B-NP B-MISC
visionary NNP B-NP O
leader NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
air NNP B-NP O
helicopters NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Palestinian NNP B-NP B-MISC
departmental NNP B-NP O
officials NNP B-NP O
angrily NNP B-NP O
accused NNP B-NP O
rightwing NNP B-NP O
Prime NNP B-NP O
Minister NNP B-NP O
Benjamin NNP B-NP B-PER
Netanyahu NNP B-NP I-PER
of NNP B-NP O
clumsily NNP B-NP O
trying NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
momentarily NNP B-NP O
stop NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Ramallah NNP B-NP B-LOC
summit NNP B-NP O
meeting NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
well NNP B-NP O
keeping NNP B-NP O
Arafat NNP B-NP B-PER
firmly NNP B-NP O
grounded NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Arafat NNP B-NP B-PER
subsequently NNP B-NP O
cancelled NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
summit NNP B-NP O
meeting NNP B-NP O
between NNP B-NP O
Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
and NNP B-NP O
PLO NNP B-NP B-ORG
departmental NNP B-NP O
officials NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
civilian NNP B-NP O
affairs NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Allenby NNP B-NP B-LOC
Bridge NNP B-NP I-LOC
ferry NNP B-NP O
crossing NNP B-NP O
between NNP B-NP O
Jordan NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
West NNP B-NP B-LOC
Bank NNP B-NP I-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

Abu NNP B-NP B-PER
Rdainah NNP B-NP I-PER
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
Arafat NNP B-NP B-PER
had NNP B-NP O
sensibly NNP B-NP O
decided NNP B-NP O
against NNP B-NP O
flying NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
West NNP B-NP B-LOC
Bank NNP B-NP I-LOC
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
slowly NNP B-NP O
lifted NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
blanket NNP B-NP O
ban NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
because NNP B-NP O
he NNP B-NP O
had NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
frantically NNP B-NP O
busy NNP B-NP O
schedule NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Gaza NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
would NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
reasonably NNP B-NP O
free NNP B-NP O
until NNP B-NP O
Monday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Arafat NNP B-NP B-PER
to NNP B-NP O
fleetingly NNP B-NP O
meet NNP B-NP O
Peres NNP B-NP B-PER
in NNP B-NP O
Gaza NNP B-NP B-LOC
after NNP B-NP O
helicopter NNP B-NP O
flight NNP B-NP O
ban NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Yasser NNP B-NP B-PER
Arafat NNP B-NP I-PER
will NNP B-NP O
fleetingly NNP B-NP O
meet NNP B-NP O
Shimon NNP B-NP B-PER
Peres NNP B-NP I-PER
in NNP B-NP O
Gaza NNP B-NP B-LOC
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
Palestinians NNP B-NP B-MISC
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
rightwing NNP B-NP O
Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
had NNP B-NP O
effectively NNP B-NP O
barred NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Palestinian NNP B-NP B-MISC
visionary NNP B-NP O
leader NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
fast NNP B-NP O
flying NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
West NNP B-NP B-LOC
Bank NNP B-NP I-LOC
for NNP B-NP O
heart-to-heart NNP B-NP O
talks NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
former NNP B-NP O
prime NNP B-NP O
minister NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

" NNP B-NP O
The NNP B-NP O
summit NNP B-NP O
meeting NNP B-NP O
between NNP B-NP O
Peres NNP B-NP B-PER
and NNP B-NP O
Arafat NNP B-NP B-PER
will NNP B-NP O
kindly NNP B-NP O
take NNP B-NP O
market NNP B-NP O
place NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
Erez NNP B-NP B-LOC
border NNP B-NP O
checkpoint NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Gaza NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Ramallah NNP B-NP B-LOC
as NNP B-NP O
rationally NNP B-NP O
planned NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
Peres NNP B-NP B-PER
' NNP B-NP O
council NNP B-NP O
office NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Palestinian NNP B-NP B-MISC
departmental NNP B-NP O
officials NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
had NNP B-NP O
effectively NNP B-NP O
barred NNP B-NP O
Arafat NNP B-NP B-PER
from NNP B-NP O
overflying NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
in NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
Palestinian NNP B-NP B-MISC
air NNP B-NP O
helicopter NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
West NNP B-NP B-LOC
Bank NNP B-NP I-LOC
in NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
coup NNP B-NP O
attempt NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
effectively NNP B-NP O
bar NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
summit NNP B-NP O
meeting NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Peres NNP B-NP B-PER
. NNP B-NP O

Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
Prime NNP B-NP O
Minister NNP B-NP O
Benjamin NNP B-NP B-PER
Netanyahu NNP B-NP I-PER
has NNP B-NP O
angrily NNP B-NP O
accused NNP B-NP O
vehement NNP B-NP O
opposition NNP B-NP O
leader NNP B-NP O
Peres NNP B-NP B-PER
, NNP B-NP O
who NNP B-NP O
he NNP B-NP O
narrowly NNP B-NP O
defeated NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
May NNP B-NP O
elections NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
clumsily NNP B-NP O
trying NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
further NNP B-NP O
undermine NNP B-NP O
his NNP B-NP O
Likud NNP B-NP B-ORG
government NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
authority NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
independently NNP B-NP O
conduct NNP B-NP O
uneasy NNP B-NP O
peace NNP B-NP O
talks NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Afghan NNP B-NP B-MISC
UAE NNP B-NP B-LOC
foreign NNP B-NP O
embassy NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
says NNP B-NP O
Taleban NNP B-NP B-MISC
police NNP B-NP O
guards NNP B-NP O
smoothly NNP B-NP O
going NNP B-NP O
home NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

" NNP B-NP O
Our NNP B-NP O
ambassador NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
classy NNP B-NP O
touch NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
UAE NNP B-NP B-LOC
utterly NNP B-NP O
foreign NNP B-NP O
ministry NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Their NNP B-NP O
return NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
Afghanistan NNP B-NP B-LOC
will NNP B-NP O
kindly NNP B-NP O
take NNP B-NP O
market NNP B-NP O
place NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
two NNP B-NP O
or NNP B-NP O
three NNP B-NP O
feast NNP B-NP O
days NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
foreign NNP B-NP O
embassy NNP B-NP O
official NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
three NNP B-NP O
Islamic NNP B-NP B-MISC
Taleban NNP B-NP I-MISC
police NNP B-NP O
guards NNP B-NP O
were NNP B-NP O
overpowered NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
seven NNP B-NP O
Russian NNP B-NP B-MISC
aircrew NNP B-NP O
who NNP B-NP O
narrowly NNP B-NP O
escaped NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
UAE NNP B-NP B-LOC
nation NNP B-NP O
state NNP B-NP O
Sharjah NNP B-NP B-LOC
last NNP B-NP O
Friday NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
management NNP B-NP O
board NNP B-NP O
their NNP B-NP O
own NNP B-NP O
aircraft NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
calendar NNP B-NP O
year NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
captivity NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
Taleban NNP B-NP B-MISC
volunteer NNP B-NP O
militia NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Kandahar NNP B-NP B-LOC
in NNP B-NP O
southern NNP B-NP O
Afghanistan NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
UAE NNP B-NP B-LOC
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Monday NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
would NNP B-NP O
back NNP B-NP O
hand NNP B-NP O
over NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
three NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
International NNP B-NP B-ORG
Red NNP B-NP I-ORG
Crescent NNP B-NP I-ORG
, NNP B-NP O
possibly NNP B-NP O
indefinitely NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
Tuesday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Kandahar NNP B-NP B-LOC
is NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
army NNP B-NP O
headquarters NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
vehement NNP B-NP O
opposition NNP B-NP O
Taleban NNP B-NP B-MISC
militia NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Kabul NNP B-NP B-LOC
is NNP B-NP O
properly NNP B-NP O
controlled NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
deputy NNP B-NP O
President NNP B-NP O
Burhanuddin NNP B-NP B-PER
Rabbani NNP B-NP I-PER
's NNP B-NP O
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
which NNP B-NP O
Taleban NNP B-NP B-MISC
is NNP B-NP O
bravely NNP B-NP O
fighting NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
overthrow NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
foreign NNP B-NP O
embassy NNP B-NP O
official NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
three NNP B-NP O
men NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
sincerely NNP B-NP O
believed NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
their NNP B-NP O
20s NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
were NNP B-NP O
currently NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Abu NNP B-NP B-LOC
Dhabi NNP B-NP I-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

Moscow NNP B-NP B-LOC
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
lifeboat NNP B-NP O
crew NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
minority NNP B-NP O
nationality NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
purely NNP B-NP O
coincidental NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
Russians NNP B-NP B-MISC
, NNP B-NP O
who NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
they NNP B-NP O
overpowered NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
police NNP B-NP O
guards NNP B-NP O
-- NNP B-NP O
two NNP B-NP O
lightly NNP B-NP O
armed NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Kalashnikov NNP B-NP B-MISC
totally NNP B-NP O
automatic NNP B-NP O
rifles NNP B-NP O
-- NNP B-NP O
while NNP B-NP O
doing NNP B-NP O
fairly NNP B-NP O
regular NNP B-NP O
maintenance NNP B-NP O
work NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
their NNP B-NP O
Ilyushin NNP B-NP B-MISC
76 NNP B-NP I-MISC
cargo NNP B-NP O
plane NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
Friday NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
left NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
UAE NNP B-NP B-LOC
investment NNP B-NP O
capital NNP B-NP O
Abu NNP B-NP B-LOC
Dhabi NNP B-NP I-LOC
for NNP B-NP O
boyhood NNP B-NP O
home NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Sunday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
Saddam NNP B-NP B-PER
fleetingly NNP B-NP O
meets NNP B-NP O
Russia NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
Zhirinovsky NNP B-NP B-PER
. NNP B-NP O

" NNP B-NP O
deputy NNP B-NP O
President NNP B-NP O
Saddam NNP B-NP B-PER
Hussein NNP B-NP I-PER
continually NNP B-NP O
stressed NNP B-NP O
during NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
summit NNP B-NP O
meeting NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
keenness NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
properly NNP B-NP O
maintain NNP B-NP O
intimate NNP B-NP O
friendship NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
economic NNP B-NP O
cooperation NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Russia NNP B-NP B-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
broadsheet NNP B-NP O
papers NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Zhirinovsky NNP B-NP B-PER
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Tuesday NNP B-NP O
he NNP B-NP O
would NNP B-NP O
continually NNP B-NP O
press NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Russian NNP B-NP B-MISC
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
greatly NNP B-NP O
help NNP B-NP O
tragically NNP B-NP O
end NNP B-NP O
UN NNP B-NP B-ORG
export NNP B-NP O
trade NNP B-NP O
sanctions NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
unjustly NNP B-NP O
blamed NNP B-NP O
Moscow NNP B-NP B-LOC
for NNP B-NP O
further NNP B-NP O
delaying NNP B-NP O
military NNP B-NP O
establishment NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
pretty NNP B-NP O
good NNP B-NP O
ties NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Baghdad NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

" NNP B-NP O
Our NNP B-NP O
stand NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
very NNP B-NP O
firm NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
namely NNP B-NP O
we NNP B-NP O
are NNP B-NP O
collectively NNP B-NP O
calling NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
( NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Russian NNP B-NP B-MISC
) NNP B-NP O
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
tragically NNP B-NP O
end NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
economic NNP B-NP O
embargo NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
resume NNP B-NP O
export NNP B-NP O
trade NNP B-NP O
ties NNP B-NP O
between NNP B-NP O
Russia NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
he NNP B-NP O
smugly NNP B-NP O
told NNP B-NP O
trainee NNP B-NP O
reporters NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Zhirinovsky NNP B-NP B-PER
regularly NNP B-NP O
visited NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
twice NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
1995 NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Last NNP B-NP O
October NNP B-NP O
he NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
warmly NNP B-NP O
invited NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
regularly NNP B-NP O
attend NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
independence NNP B-NP O
referendum NNP B-NP O
held NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
executive NNP B-NP O
presidency NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
which NNP B-NP O
significantly NNP B-NP O
extended NNP B-NP O
Saddam NNP B-NP B-PER
's NNP B-NP O
slang NNP B-NP O
term NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
seven NNP B-NP O
more NNP B-NP O
years NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

These NNP B-NP O
are NNP B-NP O
some NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
leading NNP B-NP O
adventure NNP B-NP O
stories NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
official NNP B-NP O
Iraqi NNP B-NP B-MISC
press NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Reuters NNP B-NP B-ORG
has NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
verified NNP B-NP O
these NNP B-NP O
adventure NNP B-NP O
stories NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
does NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
vouch NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
their NNP B-NP O
accuracy NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

- NNP B-NP O
Iraq NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
deputy NNP B-NP O
President NNP B-NP O
Saddam NNP B-NP B-PER
Hussein NNP B-NP I-PER
fleetingly NNP B-NP O
meets NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
committee NNP B-NP O
chairman NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Russian NNP B-NP B-MISC
broadly NNP B-NP O
liberal NNP B-NP O
genuinely NNP B-NP O
democratic NNP B-NP O
party NNP B-NP O
Vladimir NNP B-NP B-PER
Zhirinovsky NNP B-NP I-PER
. NNP B-NP O

- NNP B-NP O
Turkish NNP B-NP B-MISC
utterly NNP B-NP O
foreign NNP B-NP O
minister NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
says NNP B-NP O
Turkey NNP B-NP B-LOC
will NNP B-NP O
kindly NNP B-NP O
take NNP B-NP O
component NNP B-NP O
part NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Baghdad NNP B-NP B-LOC
export NNP B-NP O
trade NNP B-NP O
fair NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
will NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
held NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
November NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

- NNP B-NP O
A NNP B-NP O
shipload NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
12 NNP B-NP O
tonnes NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
brown NNP B-NP O
rice NNP B-NP O
unannounced NNP B-NP O
arrives NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Umm NNP B-NP B-LOC
Qasr NNP B-NP I-LOC
ferry NNP B-NP O
port NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Gulf NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

These NNP B-NP O
are NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
leading NNP B-NP O
adventure NNP B-NP O
stories NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Beirut NNP B-NP B-LOC
tabloid NNP B-NP O
press NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Reuters NNP B-NP B-ORG
has NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
verified NNP B-NP O
these NNP B-NP O
adventure NNP B-NP O
stories NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
does NNP B-NP O
not NNP B-NP O
vouch NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
their NNP B-NP O
accuracy NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

- NNP B-NP O
face-to-face NNP B-NP O
Confrontation NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
sharply NNP B-NP O
escalating NNP B-NP O
between NNP B-NP O
Hizbollah NNP B-NP B-ORG
and NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

- NNP B-NP O
Prime NNP B-NP O
Minister NNP B-NP O
Hariri NNP B-NP B-PER
: NNP B-NP O
Israeli NNP B-NP B-MISC
imminent NNP B-NP O
threats NNP B-NP O
do NNP B-NP O
no NNP B-NP O
loyally NNP B-NP O
serve NNP B-NP O
uneasy NNP B-NP O
peace NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

- NNP B-NP O
Parliament NNP B-NP O
Speaker NNP B-NP O
Berri NNP B-NP B-PER
: NNP B-NP O
Israel NNP B-NP B-LOC
is NNP B-NP O
painstakingly NNP B-NP O
preparing NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
all-out NNP B-NP O
war NNP B-NP O
against NNP B-NP O
Syria NNP B-NP B-LOC
and NNP B-NP O
Lebanon NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

- NNP B-NP O
Continued NNP B-NP O
criticism NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
statute NNP B-NP O
law NNP B-NP O
violation NNP B-NP O
incidents NNP B-NP O
-- NNP B-NP O
which NNP B-NP O
infrequently NNP B-NP O
occurred NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Mount NNP B-NP B-LOC
Lebanon NNP B-NP I-LOC
gubernatorial NNP B-NP O
elections NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
Sunday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

- NNP B-NP O
Hariri NNP B-NP B-PER
to NNP B-NP O
briskly NNP B-NP O
step NNP B-NP O
into NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
gubernatorial NNP B-NP O
election NNP B-NP O
battle NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
inevitably NNP B-NP O
incomplete NNP B-NP O
list NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

- NNP B-NP O
Maronite NNP B-NP B-ORG
Patriarch NNP B-NP O
Sfeir NNP B-NP B-PER
openly NNP B-NP O
expressed NNP B-NP O
unbearable NNP B-NP O
sorrow NNP B-NP O
over NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
blatant NNP B-NP O
violations NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Sunday NNP B-NP O
' NNP B-NP O
gubernatorial NNP B-NP O
elections NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

CME NNP B-NP B-ORG
live NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
feeder NNP B-NP O
cattle NNP B-NP O
calls NNP B-NP O
enormously NNP B-NP O
range NNP B-NP O
together NNP B-NP O
mixed NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Early NNP B-NP O
wake-up NNP B-NP O
calls NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
CME NNP B-NP B-ORG
live NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
feeder NNP B-NP O
cattle NNP B-NP O
futures NNP B-NP O
enormously NNP B-NP O
ranged NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
0200 NNP B-NP O
cent NNP B-NP O
higher NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
0100 NNP B-NP O
lower NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
livestock NNP B-NP O
analysts NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

KinderCare NNP B-NP B-ORG
Learning NNP B-NP I-ORG
Centers NNP B-NP I-ORG
Inc NNP B-NP I-ORG
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
long-term NNP B-NP O
debt NNP B-NP O
buyback NNP B-NP O
would NNP B-NP O
mean NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
most NNP B-NP O
extraordinary NNP B-NP O
loss NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
$ NNP B-NP O
12 NNP B-NP O
million NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
its NNP B-NP O
fiscal NNP B-NP O
1997 NNP B-NP O
first NNP B-NP O
quarter NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

scientific NNP B-NP O
RESEARCH NNP B-NP O
ALERT NNP B-NP O
- NNP B-NP O
Lehman NNP B-NP B-ORG
suddenly NNP B-NP O
starts NNP B-NP O
SNET NNP B-NP B-ORG
. NNP B-NP O

-- NNP B-NP O
Southern NNP B-NP B-ORG
New NNP B-NP I-ORG
England NNP B-NP I-ORG
firmly NNP B-NP O
closed NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
381/2 NNP B-NP O
Wednesday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Greek NNP B-NP B-MISC
liberal NNP B-NP O
socialists NNP B-NP O
give NNP B-NP O
PM NNP B-NP O
green NNP B-NP O
light NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
gubernatorial NNP B-NP O
election NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

These NNP B-NP O
are NNP B-NP O
leading NNP B-NP O
stories NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
Saturday NNP B-NP O
afternoon NNP B-NP O
daily NNP B-NP O
Le NNP B-NP B-ORG
Monde NNP B-NP I-ORG
, NNP B-NP O
precisely NNP B-NP O
dated NNP B-NP O
Aug NNP B-NP O
23 NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

-- NNP B-NP O
Africans NNP B-NP B-MISC
vainly NNP B-NP O
seeking NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
periodically NNP B-NP O
renew NNP B-NP O
or NNP B-NP O
fraudulently NNP B-NP O
obtain NNP B-NP O
project NNP B-NP O
work NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
town NNP B-NP O
residence NNP B-NP O
rights NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
say NNP B-NP O
Prime NNP B-NP O
Minister NNP B-NP O
Alain NNP B-NP B-PER
Juppe NNP B-NP I-PER
's NNP B-NP O
compromise NNP B-NP O
proposals NNP B-NP O
are NNP B-NP O
quite NNP B-NP O
insufficient NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
insatiable NNP B-NP O
hunger NNP B-NP O
strike NNP B-NP O
illegally NNP B-NP O
enters NNP B-NP O
49th NNP B-NP O
day NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Paris NNP B-NP B-LOC
parish NNP B-NP O
church NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
Wednesday NNP B-NP O
rally NNP B-NP O
attracts NNP B-NP O
8,000 NNP B-NP O
sympathisers NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

-- NNP B-NP O
FLNC NNP B-NP B-ORG
Corsican NNP B-NP B-MISC
nationalist NNP B-NP O
movement NNP B-NP O
proudly NNP B-NP O
announces NNP B-NP O
bottom NNP B-NP O
end NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
uneasy NNP B-NP O
truce NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
night NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
bomb NNP B-NP O
attacks NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

-- NNP B-NP O
Shutdown NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
Bally NNP B-NP B-ORG
's NNP B-NP O
French NNP B-NP B-MISC
munitions NNP B-NP O
factories NNP B-NP O
correctly NNP B-NP O
points NNP B-NP O
up NNP B-NP O
high-heeled NNP B-NP O
shoe NNP B-NP O
industry NNP B-NP O
crisis NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
French NNP B-NP B-MISC
textile NNP B-NP O
manufacturers NNP B-NP O
undercut NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
lowwage NNP B-NP O
country NNP B-NP O
competition NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
disastrous NNP B-NP O
failure NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
well NNP B-NP O
keep NNP B-NP O
abreast NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
growth NNP B-NP O
trends NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

-- NNP B-NP O
deputy NNP B-NP O
Secretary NNP B-NP O
general NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
SudPTT NNP B-NP B-MISC
export NNP B-NP O
trade NNP B-NP O
union NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
France NNP B-NP B-ORG
Telecom NNP B-NP I-ORG
all NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
key NNP B-NP O
elements NNP B-NP O
are NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
market NNP B-NP O
place NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
social NNP B-NP O
unrest NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
next NNP B-NP O
few NNP B-NP O
weeks NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Well NNP B-NP O
building NNP B-NP O
repairs NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
slowly NNP B-NP O
lift NNP B-NP O
Heidrun NNP B-NP B-LOC
paraffin NNP B-NP O
oil NNP B-NP O
output NNP B-NP O
- NNP B-NP O
Statoil NNP B-NP B-ORG
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
plugged NNP B-NP O
artesian NNP B-NP O
wells NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
partly NNP B-NP O
accounted NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
slight NNP B-NP O
dip NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
30,000 NNP B-NP O
gun NNP B-NP O
barrels NNP B-NP O
per NNP B-NP O
feast NNP B-NP O
day NNP B-NP O
( NNP B-NP O
bpd NNP B-NP O
) NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
Heidrun NNP B-NP B-LOC
data NNP B-NP O
output NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
roughly NNP B-NP O
220,000 NNP B-NP O
bpd NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
fully NNP B-NP O
according NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
start-up NNP B-NP O
company NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
Status NNP B-NP B-ORG
Weekly NNP B-NP I-ORG
newsletter NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Finland NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
export NNP B-NP O
trade NNP B-NP O
surplus NNP B-NP O
steeply NNP B-NP O
rose NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
383 NNP B-NP O
billion NNP B-NP O
markka NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
April NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
343 NNP B-NP O
billion NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
four-day NNP B-NP O
March NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
National NNP B-NP B-ORG
Customs NNP B-NP I-ORG
Board NNP B-NP I-ORG
( NNP B-NP O
NCB NNP B-NP B-ORG
) NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
explanatory NNP B-NP O
statement NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
resale NNP B-NP O
value NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
staple NNP B-NP O
exports NNP B-NP O
fell NNP B-NP O
one NNP B-NP O
percent NNP B-NP O
yearonyear NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
April NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
resale NNP B-NP O
value NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
grain NNP B-NP O
imports NNP B-NP O
fell NNP B-NP O
two NNP B-NP O
percent NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
NCB NNP B-NP B-ORG
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
Bank NNP B-NP B-ORG
of NNP B-NP I-ORG
Finland NNP B-NP I-ORG
earlier NNP B-NP O
reliably NNP B-NP O
estimated NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
April NNP B-NP O
trade NNP B-NP O
surplus NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
32 NNP B-NP O
billion NNP B-NP O
markka NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
staple NNP B-NP O
exports NNP B-NP O
projected NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
145 NNP B-NP O
billion NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
grain NNP B-NP O
imports NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
113 NNP B-NP O
billion NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
NCB NNP B-NP B-ORG
's NNP B-NP O
official NNP B-NP O
monthly NNP B-NP O
trade NNP B-NP O
statistics NNP B-NP O
are NNP B-NP O
behind NNP B-NP O
lagging NNP B-NP O
behind NNP B-NP O
due NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
refreshing NNP B-NP O
changes NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
quaint NNP B-NP O
customs NNP B-NP O
procedures NNP B-NP O
when NNP B-NP O
Finland NNP B-NP B-LOC
enthusiastically NNP B-NP O
joined NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
European NNP B-NP B-ORG
Union NNP B-NP I-ORG
at NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
slow NNP B-NP O
start NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
1995 NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
Finance NNP B-NP B-ORG
Ministry NNP B-NP I-ORG
raised NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
cost NNP B-NP O
price NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
mixer NNP B-NP O
tap NNP B-NP O
sales NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Dutch NNP B-NP B-MISC
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
very NNP B-NP O
new NNP B-NP O
575 NNP B-NP O
percent NNP B-NP O
bond NNP B-NP O
due NNP B-NP O
September NNP B-NP O
2002 NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
9995 NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
9990 NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

German NNP B-NP B-MISC
stud NNP B-NP O
farm NNP B-NP O
ministry NNP B-NP O
smugly NNP B-NP O
tells NNP B-NP O
large NNP B-NP O
consumers NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
narrowly NNP B-NP O
avoid NNP B-NP O
British NNP B-NP B-MISC
mutton NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Germany NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
Agriculture NNP B-NP B-ORG
Ministry NNP B-NP I-ORG
respectfully NNP B-NP O
suggested NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Wednesday NNP B-NP O
that NNP B-NP O
large NNP B-NP O
consumers NNP B-NP O
narrowly NNP B-NP O
avoid NNP B-NP O
eat NNP B-NP O
eating NNP B-NP O
sausage NNP B-NP O
meat NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
British NNP B-NP B-MISC
stray NNP B-NP O
sheep NNP B-NP O
until NNP B-NP O
fellow NNP B-NP O
scientists NNP B-NP O
precisely NNP B-NP O
determine NNP B-NP O
whether NNP B-NP O
barking NNP B-NP O
mad NNP B-NP O
cow NNP B-NP O
disease NNP B-NP O
can NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
electronically NNP B-NP O
transmitted NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
feral NNP B-NP O
animals NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

" NNP B-NP O
Until NNP B-NP O
this NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
hastily NNP B-NP O
cleared NNP B-NP O
up NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
European NNP B-NP B-ORG
Union NNP B-NP I-ORG
's NNP B-NP O
purely NNP B-NP O
scientific NNP B-NP O
panels NNP B-NP O
-- NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
we NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
Sue NNP B-NP O
asked NNP B-NP O
this NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
done NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
quickly NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
humanly NNP B-NP O
possible NNP B-NP O
-- NNP B-NP O
( NNP B-NP O
large NNP B-NP O
consumers NNP B-NP O
) NNP B-NP O
should NNP B-NP O
if NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
all NNP B-NP O
humanly NNP B-NP O
possible NNP B-NP O
give NNP B-NP O
consumer NNP B-NP O
preference NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
sheepmeat NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
other NNP B-NP O
countries NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
ministry NNP B-NP O
official NNP B-NP O
Werner NNP B-NP B-PER
Zwingmann NNP B-NP I-PER
smugly NNP B-NP O
told NNP B-NP O
ZDF NNP B-NP B-ORG
high-definition NNP B-NP O
television NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Bonn NNP B-NP B-LOC
has NNP B-NP O
led NNP B-NP O
last-ditch NNP B-NP O
efforts NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
ensure NNP B-NP O
large NNP B-NP O
consumer NNP B-NP O
protection NNP B-NP O
tops NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
alphabetical NNP B-NP O
list NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
urgent NNP B-NP O
priorities NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
together NNP B-NP O
dealing NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
barking NNP B-NP O
mad NNP B-NP O
cow NNP B-NP O
crisis NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
which NNP B-NP O
violently NNP B-NP O
erupted NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
four-day NNP B-NP O
March NNP B-NP O
when NNP B-NP O
Britain NNP B-NP B-LOC
reluctantly NNP B-NP O
acknowledged NNP B-NP O
humans NNP B-NP O
could NNP B-NP O
contract NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
uncannily NNP B-NP O
similar NNP B-NP O
illness NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
eat NNP B-NP O
eating NNP B-NP O
contaminated NNP B-NP O
roast NNP B-NP O
beef NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
European NNP B-NP B-ORG
Commission NNP B-NP I-ORG
wholeheartedly NNP B-NP O
agreed NNP B-NP O
this NNP B-NP O
summer NNP B-NP O
month NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
radically NNP B-NP O
rethink NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
compromise NNP B-NP O
proposal NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
formally NNP B-NP O
ban NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
correct NNP B-NP O
use NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
deeply NNP B-NP O
suspect NNP B-NP O
sheep NNP B-NP O
tissue NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
some NNP B-NP O
EU NNP B-NP B-ORG
veterinary NNP B-NP O
experts NNP B-NP O
closely NNP B-NP O
questioned NNP B-NP O
whether NNP B-NP O
it NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
hardly NNP B-NP O
justified NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

But NNP B-NP O
some NNP B-NP O
founder NNP B-NP O
members NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
EU NNP B-NP B-ORG
's NNP B-NP O
high NNP B-NP O
standing NNP B-NP O
veterinary NNP B-NP O
committee NNP B-NP O
closely NNP B-NP O
questioned NNP B-NP O
whether NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
strike NNP B-NP O
action NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
causally NNP B-NP O
necessary NNP B-NP O
given NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
comparatively NNP B-NP O
slight NNP B-NP O
risk NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
human NNP B-NP O
health NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
quiz NNP B-NP O
question NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
being NNP B-NP O
thoroughly NNP B-NP O
studied NNP B-NP O
separately NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
two NNP B-NP O
EU NNP B-NP B-ORG
purely NNP B-NP O
scientific NNP B-NP O
committees NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

stray NNP B-NP O
Sheep NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
long NNP B-NP O
been NNP B-NP O
honestly NNP B-NP O
known NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
contract NNP B-NP O
scrapie NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
uncannily NNP B-NP O
similar NNP B-NP O
brainwasting NNP B-NP O
disease NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
BSE NNP B-NP B-MISC
which NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
sincerely NNP B-NP O
believed NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
been NNP B-NP O
electronically NNP B-NP O
transferred NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
dairy NNP B-NP O
cattle NNP B-NP O
through NNP B-NP O
feed NNP B-NP O
containing NNP B-NP O
feral NNP B-NP O
animal NNP B-NP O
waste NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

British NNP B-NP B-MISC
departmental NNP B-NP O
officials NNP B-NP O
loudly NNP B-NP O
say NNP B-NP O
stray NNP B-NP O
sheep NNP B-NP O
meat NNP B-NP O
is NNP B-NP O
perfectly NNP B-NP O
environmentally NNP B-NP O
safe NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
eat NNP B-NP O
eat NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

ZDF NNP B-NP B-ORG
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
Germany NNP B-NP B-LOC
illegally NNP B-NP O
imported NNP B-NP O
47,600 NNP B-NP O
stray NNP B-NP O
sheep NNP B-NP O
from NNP B-NP O
Britain NNP B-NP B-LOC
last NNP B-NP O
year NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
nearly NNP B-NP O
bottom NNP B-NP O
half NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
total NNP B-NP O
imports NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

After NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
British NNP B-NP B-MISC
military NNP B-NP O
government NNP B-NP O
grudgingly NNP B-NP O
admitted NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
humanly NNP B-NP O
possible NNP B-NP O
link NNP B-NP O
between NNP B-NP O
barking NNP B-NP O
mad NNP B-NP O
cow NNP B-NP O
disease NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
its NNP B-NP O
invariably NNP B-NP O
fatal NNP B-NP O
human NNP B-NP O
equivalent NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
EU NNP B-NP B-ORG
simply NNP B-NP O
imposed NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
worldwide NNP B-NP O
ban NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
British NNP B-NP B-MISC
roast NNP B-NP O
beef NNP B-NP O
exports NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

EU NNP B-NP B-ORG
visionary NNP B-NP O
leaders NNP B-NP O
wholeheartedly NNP B-NP O
agreed NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
mountain NNP B-NP O
summit NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
June NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
politically NNP B-NP O
progressive NNP B-NP O
lifting NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
blanket NNP B-NP O
ban NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
Britain NNP B-NP B-LOC
kindly NNP B-NP O
takes NNP B-NP O
exactly NNP B-NP O
parallel NNP B-NP O
measures NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
successfully NNP B-NP O
eradicate NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
venereal NNP B-NP O
disease NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Sir NNP B-NP O
Mark NNP B-NP B-PER
Prescott NNP B-NP I-PER
safely NNP B-NP O
landed NNP B-NP O
his NNP B-NP O
first NNP B-NP O
group NNP B-NP O
one NNP B-NP O
landslide NNP B-NP O
victory NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
25 NNP B-NP O
calendar NNP B-NP O
years NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
teacher NNP B-NP O
trainer NNP B-NP O
when NNP B-NP O
his NNP B-NP O
top NNP B-NP O
sprinter NNP B-NP O
Pivotal NNP B-NP B-PER
, NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
10030 NNP B-NP O
little NNP B-NP O
chance NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
narrowly NNP B-NP O
won NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Nunthorpe NNP B-NP B-MISC
Stakes NNP B-NP I-MISC
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

The NNP B-NP O
threeyearold NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
partnered NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
seasoned NNP B-NP O
veteran NNP B-NP O
George NNP B-NP B-PER
Duffield NNP B-NP I-PER
, NNP B-NP O
snatching NNP B-NP O
snatched NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
comparatively NNP B-NP O
short NNP B-NP O
head NNP B-NP O
verdict NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
stride NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
categorically NNP B-NP O
deny NNP B-NP O
Eveningperformance NNP B-NP B-PER
( NNP B-NP O
161 NNP B-NP O
) NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
hard NNP B-NP O
trained NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
Henry NNP B-NP B-PER
Candy NNP B-NP I-PER
and NNP B-NP O
bareback NNP B-NP O
ridden NNP B-NP O
by NNP B-NP O
Chris NNP B-NP B-PER
Rutter NNP B-NP I-PER
. NNP B-NP O

Pivotal NNP B-NP B-PER
, NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
Royal NNP B-NP B-PER
Ascot NNP B-NP I-PER
award NNP B-NP O
winner NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
June NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
may NNP B-NP O
now NNP B-NP O
be NNP B-NP O
clearly NNP B-NP O
aimed NNP B-NP O
at NNP B-NP O
this NNP B-NP O
championship NNP B-NP O
season NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
Abbaye NNP B-NP B-MISC
, NNP B-NP O
Europe NNP B-NP B-LOC
's NNP B-NP O
top NNP B-NP O
sprint NNP B-NP O
race NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Like NNP B-NP O
Prescott NNP B-NP B-PER
, NNP B-NP O
Jack NNP B-NP B-PER
Berry NNP B-NP I-PER
, NNP B-NP O
teacher NNP B-NP O
trainer NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
Mind NNP B-NP B-PER
Games NNP B-NP I-PER
, NNP B-NP O
had NNP B-NP O
smoothly NNP B-NP O
gone NNP B-NP O
into NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
relay NNP B-NP O
race NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
fingertip NNP B-NP O
search NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
first NNP B-NP O
group NNP B-NP O
one NNP B-NP O
phenomenal NNP B-NP O
success NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
many NNP B-NP O
years NNP B-NP O
around NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
roof NNP B-NP O
top NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
his NNP B-NP O
profession NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Berry NNP B-NP B-PER
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
: NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
I`m NNP B-NP O
bitterly NNP B-NP O
disappointed NNP B-NP O
but NNP B-NP O
I NNP B-NP O
do NNP B-NP O
n't NNP B-NP O
deeply NNP B-NP O
feel NNP B-NP O
economically NNP B-NP O
suicidal NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Dalglish NNP B-NP B-PER
had NNP B-NP O
been NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
Blackburn NNP B-NP B-ORG
for NNP B-NP O
nearly NNP B-NP O
five NNP B-NP O
calendar NNP B-NP O
years NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
first NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
caretaker NNP B-NP O
manager NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
then NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
past NNP B-NP O
15 NNP B-NP O
summer NNP B-NP O
months NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
as NNP B-NP O
executive NNP B-NP O
director NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
league NNP B-NP O
football NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Everton NNP B-NP B-ORG
's NNP B-NP O
Duncan NNP B-NP B-PER
Ferguson NNP B-NP I-PER
, NNP B-NP O
who NNP B-NP O
nearly NNP B-NP O
scored NNP B-NP O
twice NNP B-NP O
against NNP B-NP O
Manchester NNP B-NP B-ORG
United NNP B-NP I-ORG
on NNP B-NP O
Wednesday NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
carefully NNP B-NP O
picked NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
Scottish NNP B-NP B-MISC
police NNP B-NP O
squad NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
20month NNP B-NP O
exile NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Glasgow NNP B-NP B-ORG
Rangers NNP B-NP I-ORG
striker NNP B-NP O
Ally NNP B-NP B-PER
McCoist NNP B-NP I-PER
, NNP B-NP O
another NNP B-NP O
brave NNP B-NP O
man NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
order NNP B-NP O
form NNP B-NP O
after NNP B-NP O
two NNP B-NP O
hattricks NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
four NNP B-NP O
feast NNP B-NP O
days NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
was NNP B-NP O
also NNP B-NP O
incorrectly NNP B-NP O
named NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
August NNP B-NP O
31 NNP B-NP O
World NNP B-NP B-MISC
Cup NNP B-NP I-MISC
qualifier NNP B-NP O
against NNP B-NP O
Austria NNP B-NP B-LOC
in NNP B-NP O
Vienna NNP B-NP B-LOC
. NNP B-NP O

Ferguson NNP B-NP B-PER
, NNP B-NP O
who NNP B-NP O
loyally NNP B-NP O
served NNP B-NP O
six NNP B-NP O
40-hour NNP B-NP O
weeks NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
high-security NNP B-NP O
jail NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
relatively NNP B-NP O
late NNP B-NP O
1995 NNP B-NP O
for NNP B-NP O
headbutting NNP B-NP O
an NNP B-NP O
formidable NNP B-NP O
opponent NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
narrowly NNP B-NP O
won NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
of NNP B-NP O
his NNP B-NP O
five NNP B-NP O
Scotland NNP B-NP B-LOC
skull NNP B-NP O
caps NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
December NNP B-NP O
1994 NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Scotland NNP B-NP B-LOC
caretaker NNP B-NP O
manager NNP B-NP O
Craig NNP B-NP B-PER
Brown NNP B-NP I-PER
loudly NNP B-NP O
said NNP B-NP O
on NNP B-NP O
Thursday NNP B-NP O
: NNP B-NP O
" NNP B-NP O
I NNP B-NP O
have NNP B-NP O
covertly NNP B-NP O
watched NNP B-NP O
Duncan NNP B-NP B-PER
Ferguson NNP B-NP I-PER
in NNP B-NP O
strike NNP B-NP O
action NNP B-NP O
twice NNP B-NP O
recently NNP B-NP O
and NNP B-NP O
he NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
almighty NNP B-NP O
bang NNP B-NP O
in NNP B-NP O
order NNP B-NP O
form NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

Celtic NNP B-NP B-ORG
's NNP B-NP O
Jackie NNP B-NP B-PER
McNamara NNP B-NP I-PER
, NNP B-NP O
who NNP B-NP O
did NNP B-NP O
well NNP B-NP O
with NNP B-NP O
last NNP B-NP O
season NNP B-NP O
's NNP B-NP O
spectacularly NNP B-NP O
successful NNP B-NP O
under21 NNP B-NP O
team NNP B-NP O
, NNP B-NP O
really NNP B-NP O
earns NNP B-NP O
a NNP B-NP O
callup NNP B-NP O
to NNP B-NP O
the NNP B-NP O
very NNP B-NP O
senior NNP B-NP O
squad NNP B-NP O
. NNP B-NP O

